人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz  奈奈良  红豆包
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第二十一集
音乐台
*我在这洞穴里采爱*
*I'm mining the cave for love*
*上面的世界我不理睬*
*Don't care about the world above*
*下面湿冷阴暗*
*Down here it's dark and cold*
*我只为寻找金块*
*I'm just looking for a nugget of gold*
*安全帽虽硬  内心却温柔*
*My hat is hard but my heart is soft*
*尘土飞扬  我连连咳嗽*
*It's dusty down here and so I cough*
*工作环境虽恶劣  但我不会罢手*
*It's a dirty job but I ain't stoppin'*
*我吸入毒素  你却让人爱不释手*
*I know I'm breathin' toxins but you're lookin' foxin'*
*答应我*
*Will you be mine?*
*做我爱的煤矿*
*Coal mine*
*答应我*
*Will you be mine?*
*钻石...*
*Diamond...*
人家正看着呢
Hey, I was watching that.
被迫去听他们的演唱会已经够遭的了
Bad enough I'm being forced to go to their concert.
就好比我已经要坐电椅了
It's like I'm going to the electric chair
而你还让我看电椅的视频
and you're making me watch videos of the electric chair.
露易丝  听话
Louise, you be nice.
你们盖尔姨妈给你们弄到的门票
Your Aunt Gayle got you those tickets
她很高兴能带上你们
and she's excited to take you.
我超级兴奋的
I'm super excited.
我这一周都在练习在演唱会现场的尖叫
I've been practicing my concert scream all week.
也许还需要努力
Ah... Still ne... might need some work.
为什么要为一个破男孩组合尖叫
Why would you waste a scream on a stupid boy band?
尖叫应该留给过山车
Screams are for roller coasters
砍人狂  和老爸早晨的口气才对
or axe murderers or Dad's morning breath.
我口气也没那么重吧
Hey, it's not that bad.
-刷刷牙吧  -我刷了
- Brush your teeth. - I did.
帮我找找钥匙
Well, then, help me look for my keys.
我告诉过你除非你想永远找不到
I've told you to stop putting stuff in there
就不要往里面放东西
if you ever want to see it again.
你把我的弟弟放了进去
You put my baby brother in there
后来我就再也没见过他了
and that was the last we saw of him!
我爱你  哈维尔・贝尔彻
Javier Belcher, I love you!
不要开玩笑了  我们快要赶不上
I'm serious. We're gonna be late
吉恩的餐桌布置比赛了
for Gene's table-setting competition.
我真得去吗
Ugh. Do I really have to?
我宁愿去看男生组合的演唱会
I-I'd rather go to the boy band concert.
鲍勃  好不容易我们有孩子参加比赛了
Bob, one of our kids is actually participating in something.
我们得去  就算只是餐桌布置比赛
We're going, even if it's table-setting.
是餐桌艺术好不好
It's table-scaping.
这是在桌子上进行的最精彩的比赛
And it's the most exciting competition on four legs.
将精巧的餐桌布置
It combines accurate table-setting placement
与富有创意的主题和道具相结合
with creative themes and costumes.
我肯定实际情况比你说的要刺激得多
I'm sure it's much more exciting than it sounds.
肯定是这样的 对吗
It has to be. Right?
吉恩  话说你是怎么进到
Gene, how did you even end up going
餐桌布置比赛的地区赛的
to the regionals in table-setting, anyway?
是餐桌艺术
scaping
这是唯一的非体育类的课外活动
It was the only non-athletic after-school activity,
结果我横扫了比赛
and I creamed the competition.
正如你所见
As you can see,
垃圾主题餐桌  [《Pum Up the Volume》为一唱片名
我的桌布是一个垃圾袋
my tablecloth is a trash bag.
-请享用这罐垃圾饮料  -有意思
- Please enjoy this gar-beverage. - Amusing.
用完餐后
And when the meal is over,
你可以将脏了的餐具装在卡车里
you can deposit your dirty silverware in the truck
运往垃圾场
to head to the dump.
-我们的主题是双胞胎晚餐  -双胞餐
- Our theme is twin dinner. - Twinner!
-两把刀  -两个叉
- Two knives. - Two forks.
-两张餐巾  -两个盘子
- Two napkins. - Two plates...
恭喜你吉恩 你可以去参加地区比赛了
Congratulations, Gene. You're going to regionals.
太棒了
All right!
吉恩  既然你那么喜欢摆餐桌
Gene, if you like setting tables so much,
为何不在餐馆里
why don't you set tables at the restaurant?
或者在家里摆呢
Or here?
不  老爸
No, Dad.
我不在我吃饭的地方摆
I don't set where I eat.
盖尔姨妈怎么还没来
Where's Aunt Gayle?
这是我人生第一场演唱会
It's my first concert.
我想快点开始
I want to hurry up and start remembering
好早一点在余生回忆
this moment for the rest of my life.
也许她意识到作为一个已经42岁的妇女
Maybe Aunt Gayle realized that she's a 42-year-old woman
不该迷恋男生组合
and she shouldn't be into boy bands?
你好
Hello?
盖尔姨妈  你到了吗
Hi, Aunt Gayle. Are you outside?
有急事吗
An emergency?
有急事
Emergency?
好吧  好
Okay, yeah...
我  我理解  再见
I-I understand. Bye.
我要听坏消息  我要听坏消息
Give me the bad news. Give me the bad news!
盖尔把她的一只猫错当成
Aunt Gayle pepper-sprayed one of her cats
企图性骚扰她的闯入者
because she thought he was an intruder
朝它喷胡椒喷雾剂了
trying to sexually assault her.
她要带它去看兽医  演唱会不能去了
She has to take him to the vet and we have to miss the concert.
太好啦
Yeah!
这是盖尔姨妈继去年在手机店里
This is the best thing Aunt Gayle's done
拉了一裤兜屎后做过的最好的事了
since she pooped her pants at the cell phone store last year.
我的心刚刚也泄堤了
Ugh, my heart just pooped its pants.
好多人呀
Wow. Lots of people.
没想到餐桌布置比赛也办得有模有样的
I didn't realize that table-setting was such a big deal.
餐桌艺术
'Scaping!
看看那些奖杯
Check out those trophies.
还有戴着"评审"胸牌的评审呢
Ooh, and judges with buttons that say "Judge."
如果我想赢第一的话那得开始准备了
Well, got to get cracking if I'm gonna win first place.
宝贝  赢不赢都没有关系
You know, honey, it's okay if you don't win.
没错  吉恩  不论输赢我们都为你
Yeah, Gene, I mean, win or lose, we're just proud that...
能参加摆桌比赛骄傲
you're setting a table at the competitive level.
迷你牛角面包
Ooh, mini croissants!
如果我吃到第16个
No matter what I say,
不管我说什么你也要阻止我
stop me when I've had 16.
既然不去演唱会了
So, now that we're not going to the concert,
我们该做点什么呢
what should we do first?
好吧  我试试
All right, I'll give it a shot.
是这样吗
Is this it?
嗯  还不错
Yeah, that's good.
好吧  我不喜欢玩这个
Okay! I hate this.
蒂娜  高兴点
Come on, Tina, cheer up.
只是四个跳舞的烂男生
It's four lame boys who dance.
这世上除了他们还有好多精彩的东西呢
There's so much more out there in the world.
不  没有了
No, there isn't!
当我不是把你摞倒的那个人的时候
Ugh, it's no fun having you down
你躺在地上真是一点意思都没有
if I'm not the one who got you there.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吧  我也不是铁石心肠的人
Fine. I'm not a monster.
我会帮你的
I'll help you.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是我带你去演唱会
I mean I'll get you to the concert.
-我把你带过去  -怎么去
- I'll get you there. - How?
你确信我们就这样一直骑下去
Are you sure we can bike all the way there
就能在演唱会开始之前赶到吗
by the time the concert starts?
我们不像这样闲聊就没问题
Not if we keep chitchatting like this.
到高速公路了
Oh, here's the freeway.
进去之后马上往快车道开  知道了吗
Once we merge, get in the fast lane, okay?
我们转眼就能到了
And we'll get there in no time.
怎么了
What?
齐克  你在这里做什么
Zeke? What are you doing here?
我和我堂兄莱斯利
Me and my cousin Leslie are going to sell
要去男孩时代的演唱会外面
some bootleg T-shirts and hot dogs
卖盗版T恤和热狗
at the Boyz 4 Now concert.
应有尽有
Boom. Whatcha letcha.
来看看  均码号
Ha! Check it out. One size fits all.
该死  这台机器也说我的卡被冻结了
Damn, this one says my card's declined, too.
齐克  你有钱吗
Zeke, you have any money?
没有  我可是身无分文
Nah, my white ass is broke.
我有加油的钱
Hey, I've got gas money.
你那车里还有两个空位吗
You got room for two more in that buggy?
给我五美元  我就是你的驾车员
You slip me a fiver, I'll be your driver.
莱斯利喜欢押韵
Leslie loves rhymes.
还喜欢罐装的意大利面
And pasta that comes in cans.
不是罐头  绝不下喉
If it ain't from a can, it don't go in this man.
我从没跟这么多热狗一起在车里待过
I've never ridden with this many hot dogs before.
又是个"第一次"
A day of firsts.
当心  压坏就得掏钱买哦
Watch out. You squish 'em, you bought 'em.
男孩时代  我们来了
Boyz 4 Now, here we come.
别挤
Don't squish it!
男孩时代里你最喜欢谁
So who's your favorite Boy 4 Now?
格里芬很受欢迎  他最出格
Griffin's the hot one. And he's super extreme.
他的宠物是一只狼
His dog is a wolf.
-别说了  -还有艾伦
- Stop. - And then there's Allen.
他很可爱  但很腼腆  他的粉丝团
He's cute but shy. His fans are called
叫做"艾粉"
Allen-coholics.
我的继母是艾粉  还是个购物狂
My stepmom's an Allen-coholic. And a shopaholic.
真是雪上加霜
Double trouble!
这是马特
This is Matt.
他有点小脾气  还有点老
He's moody and a little older.
我想得有17岁了
I think, like, 17.
或者是他的胡子17  他本人90
Maybe his mustache is 17, but he's 90.
这是布布
And then there's Boo Boo.
他很年轻  但跳舞超棒
He's young but crazy good at dancing.
我以前是个不折不扣的布布迷
I used to be a real Boo Boo Booster,
但我现在有点喜欢格里芬
but now I'm kind of into Griffin.
别再说啦
Ugh, stop talking!
闭嘴  闭嘴
Stop. Stop.
-我要把拳头塞你嘴里了  -好吧
- Okay, I'm gonna put my fist in your mouth. - Okay.
玛丽莲  缺陷的美
Oh, Marilyn. Tragic beauty.
我很喜欢你儿子的布置
I love your son's table.
你好
Hi.
谢谢
Aw. Thank you.
魔术  嗯
Magic. Hmm.
你"嗯"是什么意思
Uh, what's "Hmm"?
你们摆得很好
Your table's cute.
但只有一个人能将"金盘子"带回家
But only one person can take home the Golden Plate.
反正我们是肯定不会带着"银匙"走的
And we sure didn't come to take home the Silver Spoon.
是吗  我们也不会
Yeah, well, we ne... neither did we.
-没错  -是的
- Right. - Yeah.
-是的  -是的
- Yeah. - Yeah!
得了吧  我们走  奥斯卡
Oh, please. Come on, Oscar.
你还得用黄油雕个哭泣的乔・狄马乔呢
You've still got a crying Joe DiMaggio to carve out of butter.
美国职业棒球选手
再见  各位  祝你们好运
Bye, guys. Good luck.
别跟他们说话
Don't talk to them!
吉恩  去好好装饰你的桌子
Gene, get back to work on your table.
你得赢
You've got to win.
你不是说不赢也没关系吗
I thought you said it was okay if I didn't win.
那是在遇到那个蠢货之前
Well, that was before we met that idiot.
现在赶紧的
Now, chop-chop.
老爸  你认真起来了呢
Ooh, Dad, you got the fever!
成餐桌艺术狂热分子了
'Scaping fever!
餐桌艺术还真是不容小觑啊
Whoo! Can't escape the 'scape!
-我们来干一场吧  -没错
Let's do this! Yeah!
难怪大家都不喜欢女人
Ugh, no wonder no one likes women.
好吧  演唱会结束后见
All right, see you after the show.
当心点
Be careful.
里面全是春心萌动的少女
There's a lot of puberty in there.
真不敢相信我来这儿了  这真的发生了
I can't believe I'm here. It's really happening.
我觉得有点头晕
I feel light-headed.
别晕啊
Whoa! No fainting!
我觉得我没力气自己走进去了
I don't think I'm strong enough to go in there alone.
你得陪我进去
I need you to come with me.
好吧
Fine.
我陪你到座位  免得你被踩死
I'll get you to your seat so you don't get trampled,
然后我就撤了
but then I am out of there.
你们脑子都进水了吗
What is wrong with all of you?
不就是男孩吗
They're just boys!
男孩  在哪儿
Boys? Where?
你不是吧
Oh, come on.
小家伙  你好
Hello, young man.
能给我介绍下你的餐桌吗
What can you tell me about your table?
这个吗
Oh, well...
等下  你耳朵后面是什么
Wait, what's that behind your ear?
这是你的席次卡吗
Is this your place card?
我的天
Oh! Oh, my!
现在  请就座吧
Now, please, take your seat.
允许我为您铺上餐巾
Allow me to put your napkin on your lap.
很聪明啊
Very clever.
我好像忘了准备桌面装饰品
Oh, I seem to have forgotten my centerpiece.
你说我这是忘没忘呢
Or did I?
这种情形下你会提供什么菜单
And what menu would you serve with this setting?
主菜嘛  您可以从那顶大礼帽中
For the entree, you'll pull a roasted rabbit
取出一只烤兔
out of your top hat plate.
甜点则为您送上咒语烘焙的土豆泥
Served with abracadab-braised potatoes
和魔力冰激凌三明治
and ice cream shazamwiches for dessert!
她在笑呢
She's smiling.
我看很顺利
I think it's going well.
看咱儿子状态不错还挺放松
He looks good. He looks loose.
很高兴为大家宣布晋级决赛的选手
I'm pleased to announce our four finalists:
梅丽莎・布朗  奥斯卡・安东尼
Melissa Brown, Oscar Anthony...
我晋级了  晋级了
I did it! I did it!
希瑟・史密斯
...Heather Smith
以及吉恩・贝尔彻
and Gene Belcher.
-好耶  -好棒
- Yay! - Yay!
等下  怎么有四名冠军呢
Wait, why are there four winners?
决赛选手们  请到各自的餐桌前
Finalists, please report to your table
准备第二回合的原创展示
and begin assembling your second original display.
第二回合
Second display?
如果你们认为我们的第一回合不错
If you thought our first table was good,
-你们确实这么认为  -我们并没有
- which you did... - No, we didn't.
擦亮眼睛看我们第二回合吧
...just wait until you see our second one.
我不想透露太多
I don't want to give anything away,
我们要坐火箭飞船离开地球
but we're about to take a rocket ship out of this world.
-就是太空主题呗  -我不能说
- So it's space-themed? - I can't say.
很明显就是  你刚才说了
Well, it is. You just basically said it.
不告诉你
I'll never tell.
另外 我不觉得你们第一回合有多好
Plus, i didn't think your first table was good.
我决定优雅地无视你的回应
I graciously disrespect your answer.
先看过我们的作品再说吧
Well, wait till you see what we got, okay?
我忙得很
I'm busy then.
你来都来了  早晚都要看到的
Well, you're gonna have to look at it if you're here.
我好像车没停好
I'm double-parked.
好了  决赛选手们
Okay, finalists.
各就各位  预备  开始
On your mark, get set, set.
吉恩  你怎么准备的
All right, Gene, what have you got?
最好要比外太空的主题更宏大更震撼
It better be bigger and more impressive than outer space.
不如用太空中的玛丽莲  太空玛丽莲
Or Marilyn in space. Marilyn in space.
我根本不知道还有第二回合
I didn't know there was supposed to be a second display.
什么
What?!
你没看比赛规则吗  吉恩
Did you read the rules, Gene?
没啊  那玩意有16页呢
No! There were 16 pages.
我就看到不让穿露趾鞋那行
I only got up to the part that said no open-toed shoes.
我们要怎么办  我们不能输
What are we gonna do? We can't lose.
我们都已经走这么远了
We've come too far.
走这么远  这么远
Come too far? Come too far?!
根本没走远好不好  琳
We haven't come too far, Lin!
我们才刚起步
We're just getting started!
好吧  你说我们要怎么办
Okay, so what are we gonna do?!
为什么我要这样咆哮啊
Why am I talking like this?!
我不知道啊  为什么我...
I don't know! Why am I tal...
我想是我太兴奋了
I think I'm excited!
-我的天  -太古怪了  我们必须赢
- Oh, God! - This is weird! We got to win it!
我们当冠军吧
Let's win it!
怎么了
What?
我穿了露趾鞋
I'm wearing open-toed shoes.
真讨厌
Ah, shoot.
男孩时代
Boyz 4 Now!
男孩时代  男孩时代
Boyz 4 Now! Boyz 4 Now!
好了  骚年  我看你也就位了
Okay, Teen, I think you're all set.
那我就先走了
Um, I'm gonna get out of here.
那待会见  成吗
So, I'll see you later, okay, buddy?
晚上好  女士们姑娘们
Good evening, ladies and girls!
准备好了没
Are you ready?
懂他们  爱他们
You know them, you love them!
他们是
What are they?
男  孩  时  代
Boyz... 4... Now!
男孩时代  男孩时代
Boyz 4 Now! Boyz 4 Now!
我希望那些激光灯
I hope those are the kinds of lasers
能把人劈成两半
that slice people in half.
掌声欢迎  艾伦
Please welcome... Allen!
我的妈呀
Holy crap.
格里芬
Griffin!
这么多威亚线  哪还有飞的感觉
Lot of wires. Not quite creating the illusion.
你们看见没  那边
You guys seeing this? Right there!
马特
Matt!
空中老头啊
Uh-oh. Sky Grandpa!
以及布布
And Boo Boo!
真是烂透了
This is terrible.
是谁召唤这些漂亮美眉来的啊
Who let all these pretty girls in here?
*我要听你的秘密*
*I want to hear your secrets*
*我对你很感兴趣*
*I'm so interested in you*
布布
Boo Boo!
我的天  我这是怎么了
Oh, my God, who the frig am I?!
*答应我  做我爱的煤矿*
*Will you be mine? Coal mine*
你会错过艾伦的诗独唱的
You're gonna miss Allen's poetry solo.
你不喜欢男生  你不喜欢男生
You do not like a boy. You do not like a boy!
尤其是那个叫  布布的
Especially a boy named... Boo Boo.
别再想了
Stop it!
我的天  把持住自己呀
Oh, God! Get a hold of yourself!
不
No!
布布太可爱了
Ah, Boo Boo's so cute.
可爱
Cute?
只有他那张脸蛋才配为脸  你个白痴
He's the reason faces were invented, you idiot!
*我要告诉你个秘密*
*I need to show you a secret*
*可能会吓到你*
*It's gonna be a surprise*
*再靠近我一点*
*Come a little bit closer*
*让我在你眼中密语*
*Let me whisper in your eyes*
*When I whisper in your eyes*
*别乱想  别眨眼*
*Don't think, don't blink*
*姑娘  嘘  别出声*
*Hey, girl, shh. Shush.*
*别说话  睁开眼*
*Close your lips and open your eyes.*
*我要你双眼聆听我的唇语和秋波*
*I want your eyes to hear my lips and also my eyes...*
我的天
Oh, my God!
蒂娜  蒂娜
Tina. Tina!
你不是要走吗
I thought you were leaving.
计划有变  我要跟你谈谈
Change of plans. I need to talk to you.
有几个问题问你
I have questions.
再跟我说说乐队的事
Tell me about the band again.
-可在车上你不是不想  -少废话
- But in the car, you didn't want to... - Tell me!
-艾伦...  -下一个
- Well, Allen... - Next!
格里芬的
Um, Griffin's...
知道  知道  下一个
Yeah, sure, Griffin, Griffin. Next!
-好吧  马特...  -下一个
- Okay, Matt... - Next!
那就只剩布布了
Well, that leaves Boo Boo.
是吗  我对他比较感兴趣
Oh, really? That's interesting.
再多说点布布的事
Tell me more. What about Boo Boo?
他年纪最小
Boo Boo's the youngest.
有一副好嗓子
And he's got a really great voice,
不过他还没变声  所以未来也说不好
but he hasn't hit puberty yet, so that could change.
他喜欢什么  运动吗  运动我可以的
What's he into? Sports? I could get into sports.
他还喜欢些什么
What the hell else does he like?
我想送他点东西
I want to give him things.
露易丝  你喜欢布布
Whoa, Louise. You like Boo Boo?
什么  才不是  蒂娜...
What?! No, Tina, that's...
好吧  喜欢  我喜欢上男生了
Okay, right, like, I like a boy.
真是...  你觉得他会喜欢我吗
That's... Ugh! Do you think he might like me?
我的天  我这是怎么了
Oh, my God, what's happened to me?!
把我的心掏出来看看  我被感染了
Cut me open! I'm infected! Pull it out!
没关系的  露易丝  不过是春心萌动
It's okay, Louise. You're just having a crush.
绝对不是  布布
Never! Boo Boo!
我的天  你病了  露易丝・贝尔彻
Oh, my God, you are sick, Louise Belcher.
你病入膏肓了
You are sick!
姐会陪你度过这一关的
I'm going to get you through this.
跟我说说你喜欢布布什么
Tell me what you like about Boo Boo.
都不喜欢  都喜欢  我也不知道
Nothing. Everything. I don't know.
你喜欢他的头发吗
Do you like his hair?
你是说他那让人想在雨天躲在下面避雨的
You mean those soft blond bangs
飘逸的金色刘海吗
you want to hide under like an umbrella on a rainy day?
不  不太喜欢
No, not really.
那他的脸呢
And his face?
难看死了  漂亮极了
Ew, gross, it's so gorgeous!
让我想扇他一巴掌  我想扇他
I just want to slap it. I want to slap it.
我想给他那丑恶又美丽的脸来一巴掌
I just want to slap his hideous, beautiful face.
你是想亲他吗
Um, you mean kiss?
不  我想扇他
No, I mean slap.
你真是走极端啊  姑娘
Whoa. You got it bad, girl.
我看过比赛规则了
Okay, I read the rules.
这里写说可以使用任何自带物品
It says here you can use anything you brought with you.
头脑风暴  开始吧
So brainstorm. Go.
我想到一个
Oh, I got it!
我们可以剃老爸的毛  把它们粘餐桌上
We could shave Dad, glue his hair to the table,
主题就定为"真是恶心"
and the theme could be "That's Nasty."
我们去偷别人的点子吧
Let's steal another kid's display.
什么  鲍勃  不行
What?! Bob, no.
好吧  不偷就不偷  我们不作弊
Okay, not that. We don't have to cheat.
但一定要赢
But we have to win,
尽量用正常手段
by probably not cheating.
鲍勃  你的口气  含块薄荷糖
Oh, ew, Bob, your breath. Take a mint.
你那都能闻到吗
You can smell it all the way over there?
我也不知道我怎么了  可能快死了
I don't know what's wrong with me. Maybe I'm dying.
有了  老妈的钱包  全倒出来看看
That's it! Mom's purse. Dump it out!
琳  里面好多东西说不定都能用
Yeah, Lin, there's got to be all sorts of stuff in there.
-我们看看吧  -好吧  全倒出来了
- Let's take a look. - All right, dump it.
这就是我用过的纸巾的去处啦
That's where all my wadded tissues went.
赶紧用这些东西堆个什么出来
Start making piles of stuff that could go together.
好  我有主意了
Eh... okay, I got one.
唇膏  防狼喷雾  小包胡萝卜干
Lipstick, pepper spray, tiny bag of carrots.
主题是什么
What's the theme?
"夜行女侠"
Uh, "Woman of the Night."
她梳妆打扮好  杀了一个路人
She gets dressed up, she kills a john,
再吃了点零食
she has a snack.
还是堆东西吧
Uh, let's keep making piles.
*告诉我*
*Tell me*
*每一次你泪如雨下*
*About every single time you've cried*
*第一次*
*The first time*
*是你的金鱼死去那天*
*Oh, when your goldfish died.*
太棒了
This is amazing.
8次安可
Eight encores.
通常只有7次的
They usually only do seven.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你非要唱歌的时候说话吗
Why would you talk during a song?
安静点  蒂娜
Please be quiet, Tina.
什么  不能就这样结束啊
What? They can't be done.
我还意犹未尽呢
I'm not done!
他们去哪儿
Where are they going?
后台啊
Backstage.
她们肯定有后台通行证
They probably have backstage passes.
我们也去
Uh, let's go do that.
可我们没有通行证啊
But we don't have passes.
蒂娜  你就没从他们的新歌
Tina, did you learn nothing
《姑娘  你不需要后台通行证》
from the Boyz 4 Now song,
里学到点什么吗
"Girl, You Don't Need a Backstage Pass"?
我得了不治之症链球菌性喉炎
Wish kid, fatal strep throat,
是来完成最后心愿的
coming through.
不行
Nope.
我是侦探布伦达・李・约翰逊
I'm detective Brenda Lee Johnson.
"Brenda Leigh Johnson" 美剧《罪案终结》中的女主人公
后台发生命案了
There's been a murder backstage.
谁都不能进这道门
No one gets through the door.
听着  我懂
Look, I get it.
我也想放你们过去
I'd love to let you back there.
我能看出你们的痛苦
I can see the pain in your face.
这痛苦不但不会减轻  只会越来越厉害
That pain doesn't go away; It only gets worse.
到我这年龄你们就明白了
Don't get older.
卖热狗咯  不不  再等等
Hot dogs. No, no, wait.
对对  这个熟了
Oh, yep, yep, this one's hot.
我们可以走了  齐克
We're ready to go, Zeke.
莱斯利去哪儿了
Where's Leslie?
他把卖T恤的钱拿去
He's using his shirt money to buy
找巡演车司机买濒临灭绝的箱龟了
an endangered box turtle from the tour bus driver.
巡演车
Tour bus?
总之  千万别在午夜的时候喂他吃东西
But whatever you do, don't feed him after midnight.
开玩笑的啦  他才分不清时间咧
Just kidding. He doesn't know what time it is.
难不成他戴手表了吗
What is he, wearing a watch?
嘿  兄弟
Hey, cuz.
来看看我们的新成员
Look who just joined the family.
他住在龟壳里哦  萌死了
He lives in a shell and he's cute as hell.
酷
Cool.
司机  你还有什么濒临灭绝的动物
Hey, bus driver, what other endangered animals you got in there?
我还有一只非洲产卵青蛙
Well, I got an African egg frog.
一只菊头蝠
I got a horseshoe bat.
一只蜥蜴  一只臭鼬  一只夜猴
Got a skink and a skunk. Got a bush baby...
-夜猴你卖多少  -夜猴不卖的
- How much you want for that bush baby? - Not for sale.
-拜托  -你买蜥蜴吧  附送臭鼬
- Come on. - But buy the skink, I'll throw in the skunk.
我想让格里芬在我的眼睑里面签名
I want Griffin to sign the inside of my eyelids,
这样他就是我入睡前看到的最后一样东西
so he's the last thing I see before I go to bed.
你要让布布签哪儿
What are you going to ask Boo Boo to sign?
不  蒂娜  我不要布布的签名
Oh, no, Tina. I don't want Boo Boo's signature.
跟你说了  我想扇他
I told you, I want to slap him.
他应该不会喜欢那个吧
I don't know if he'll like that.
所以我们才要偷袭
That's why it has to be a surprise attack.
我们先找个地方藏着  一会儿再跳出来
We need to find some place to burst out of.
-那儿吗  -好主意
- In there? - Uh, great idea,
但估计我们不止六英寸高
but just in case we aren't six inches tall,
那边怎么样
how about in... there?
-这里面真难闻  -是啊
- Ah, smells horrible in here. - Yeah.
要是这些气味附在我的
It would be terrible if these smells got stuck
鼻孔内就糟糕了
to the inside of my nostrils and I would
我就永远摆脱不了这吸汗带的味道了
have to smell this sweaty sweatband forever.
我感觉他们来了
I think they're coming.
让我扇布布一巴掌
I'll slap Boo Boo in the face,
我们就可以回家了
and we'll be on our way.
暗恋什么的去死吧
Crush crushed.
演出很精彩  各位
Whew. Great show, guys.
是啊  今晚我们带去了好多欢笑
Yeah. We caused a lot of smiles tonight.
必须的
Totally.
坐好了各位  今晚要在车上过夜了
Settle in guys. We've got an overnighter.
车好像开走了
I think we're moving.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们踏上巡演之旅了
We're going on tour.
扇布布之旅  我们来啦
Slapabama, here we come.
我们要现在跳出去吗
Should we jump out now?
通常这种情况都是怎么操作的
What's the protocol in this situation?
也许你不该太心急  露易丝
Maybe you shouldn't rush into this, Louise.
我们完全可以一直住这里面
We could just live in here forever.
好了  布布
All right, Boo Boo.
你得去坐儿童座椅了
We got to strap you into your booster seat.
不  我不想坐
No! I don't wanna!
你知道规矩的  等长到80磅的时候
You know the rules: When you hit 80 pounds,
-你就能坐成人座了  -不要
- you can sit in a big boy seat. - No!
各位  你们唱那歌吧
Guys, why don't you sing the song?
*坐进儿童椅*
*Gettin' into your booster seat*
*从头到脚绑结实咯*
*From your big boy head to your big boy feet*
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
不知道
I don't know.
"儿童椅"难道是毒品的暗号
Is "Booster seat" Code for drugs?
*从头到脚帮结实咯*
*From my big boy head to my big boy feet*
布布
Boo Boo!
是个女孩
Ah! It's a girl!
有女孩看见我坐儿童椅了
A girl saw me in my booster seat!
别看我
Don't look at me!
-停车  乔迪  -不  乔迪
- Stop the bus, Jody. - No, Jody,
-别停车  -谁在说话
- don't stop the bus. - Who said that?
没人  是你自己在想
No one. You were just thinking it.
-箱子里还有一个  -我停车
- We got another one in the hamper. - Stopping the bus.
嗨  我是蒂娜  你们的新巡演负责人
Hi. I'm Tina, your new roadie.
我脸上有东西吗
Do I have something on my face?
开玩笑的  我知道我脸上有五条吸汗带
Just kidding. I know it's five sweatbands.
我们会在前面的休息站让你们下车
We'll let you off at this rest stop up ahead.
那儿有电话  打给你们的父母
Hey, use the phone. Call your parents.
他们肯定在担心你们呢
They're probably worried about you.
要是我的话也会担心我女儿的
I know I'd be worried about my daughter.
如果我有女儿的话
If I had one.
但我才十七岁  所以我没有
But I'm 17, so I don't.
等等
Wait.
布布  走之前
Before we go, Boo Boo,
我妹妹有事想问你
my sister wants to ask you something.
啥
What?
啥  听起来像...
What? It sounded like...
啥  啥
What? What?
你说什么
What are you saying?
什么  啥
What? What?
给我松开
Get me out of this thing!
我在跟我的粉丝说话呢
I'm trying to talk to a fan.
能让我保留点尊严吗
Give me just a little dignity.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了  你刚刚说啥  小姑娘
Now, what was that, little girl?
-真有种  -总算值了
- Bold. - Worth it.
-我觉得我们成功了  -没错
- I think we nailed it. - Yeah.
又大胆  又有新意
It's daring, it's different.
没有人做这个
Nobody else is doing this.
让我再多放一点
I'll just put a little more
老妈包包里的草莓酱
of this strawberry jam from Mom's purse and...
搞定
done.
看看他们那桌  典型的书呆子作品
Look at their table. Nerd alert.
-我说得对吧  -没错
- Am I right? - Yeah.
来自地球的喊话  你们输了
Earth to those guys: You lose.
两位  我们这次没像往常那样选择放弃
You guys, we didn't give up like we usually do,
我觉得是值得的
and I think it really paid off.
真为我们感到骄傲
I'm proud of us.
好了  评委来了  祝你好运  吉恩
All right, here comes the judge. Good luck, Gene.
去征服评委吧  吉恩小神童
Go get 'em, Gene Bean. Yeah!
如何
Eh?
我的神啊
Oh, good Lord.
欢迎来到我的"月经餐厅"
Welcome to my "Menstru-rant."
我们不是商量好叫"姨妈作品"吗
I thought we decided on "Period Piece."
"Period Piece" 英语中固定搭配  意为"历史题材作品"  其中"period"也有"例假"的意思
愿你有好胃口  以及更年期潮热症状
Hope you brought your appetite, and your hot flashes.
我想我已经看够了
Okay, I think I've seen enough.
如你所见  餐盘旁有一张卫生棉
As you'll see, beside the plate is a sanitary napkin.
需要我帮你贴在大腿上以免有大血崩吗
May I place it on your lap in case there's a big spill?
-不  我  -请让我为你服务
- No. I... - Please, let me.
-走开  -有护翼的哦
- Get away. - It's got wings.
-给她看卫生棉条  -不用
- Show her the tampon straw. - No.
我一点都不想看卫生棉条
I don't want to see the tampon straw.
看来某人大姨妈来了哦
Someone's on the rag.
还好那两组也搞砸了
Well, at least those two got creamed, too.
天呐
Oh, God...
老爸  我还要继续参加这个比赛吗
Dad, do I have to do this again?
当然
Yes.
他们输就等于我们赢了
Them losing is like us winning.
对  我们也得了第四名呢
Yeah, and we got fourth place.
我家的孩子可没有在任何比赛里
I mean, I don't think any of our kids
得过第四名
have gotten fourth place in anything.
我是第四名  我是第四名
I'm number four! I'm number four!
我想到明年参赛的点子了
Ooh, I got an idea for next year.
-卡在井里的杰西卡宝宝  -太好了
- Baby Jessica stuck in a well. - Yes!
"baby jessica"案件 美国90年代的一起亲生父母和养父母争夺孩子的案件  媒体曾大幅报道
你得在全国观众的注视下在两天的时间里
You have to look for your dinner for two days
自己去找餐桌
as the nation watches.
谢谢你来接我们  盖尔姨妈
Thanks for coming to get us, Aunt Gayle.
这也是我该做的
It was the least I could do.
还好我的猫没事
The good news is my cat is going to be fine.
只是以后我得让它戴护目镜了
He just has to wear goggles from now on
免得同样的事再次发生
in case it happens again.
蒂娜  如果你的生活是这样的话
Tina, if that's what your life is like,
上帝啊  你活在这世上有什么意义
God, how are you even alive?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你基本上对每个你认识的男生都暗生情愫
You have a crush on almost every boy you know.
你是怎么做到的
How do you do it?
我才有三小时那样的经历已经觉得不行了
Feeling that way for three hours was way too much for me.
我没什么了不起的
I'm no hero.
和大家一样我戴胸罩也是先一边再另一边
I put my bra on one boob at a time like everyone else.
好消息是
Well, the good news is
我已经把种那感觉从我系统里删除了
that now that I got it out of my system,
以后再也不会暗恋谁了
I'm done having crushes forever.
我希望你如愿
I hope for your sake you're right.
如果不行  随时来找我
But if not, you know where I live.
你真是个坚强的女人  蒂娜
You're a strong woman, Tina.
我知道
I know.
晚安  蒂娜
Good night, Tina.
晚安  老妈
Night, Mom.
晚安  露易丝
Night, Louise.
你们今天玩得开心吗
Did you guys have fun today?
无聊透了
Pretty dull.
真倒胃口
Ugh. Disgusting.
我恨死你了  你这个白痴
I hate you so freaking much, you idiot.
扇扇
Slap.
*我要听你的秘密*
*I want to hear your secrets*
*我对你很感兴趣*
*I'm so interested in you*
*你午饭吃的什么*
*What did you have for lunch today?*
*早饭又吃了什么*
*Tell me breakfast, too*
*哪位朋友让你生气了  姑娘*
*Which friend are you mad at, girl?*
*你穿多大的鞋*
*What size are your shoes?*
*你刚刚去厕所了  是大号还是小号*
*You just went to the bathroom, number one or number two?*
*我想知道一切  关于你的一切*
*I want to know everything, everything about you*
*我要听你的秘密*
I want to hear your secrets
*我对你很感兴趣*
I'm so interested in you
*就算不是秘密*
*Even if it's not a secret*
*也可以告诉我*
*Tell me that stuff, too*
*细节  我想听细节*
*Details, I want to know details*
*你爸叫什么*
*What's your dad's name?*
*细节  细节  你妈呢*
*Details, details. And your mom's*
*你对什么过敏  细节*
*Any allergies? Details*
*你那天参加的舞会怎么样*
*How was prom?*
*有趣  非常有趣*
*Interesting, so interesting.*